{
    "id": "802b24717a3f48479ee3d94962552160",
    "title": "Both, Either Or Neither",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3d8de39bd8244b81a1385ce935c69178",
            "title": "Both, Either Or Neither",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "............................. of us were ill so we didn't go to work.",
                    "description": "Both is used in affirmative clauses to speak of two people or things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has eaten .............................. of the chops.",
                    "description": "Both means one and the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "both",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't like .................................. of the colors.",
                    "description": "Either means one or the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I liked ................................. colors.",
                    "description": "Both means one and the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have invited ................................ of them.",
                    "description": "Both means one and the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have not invited .................................... of them.",
                    "description": "Instead of writing both ...not, we use not either or neither.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. key opens the door.",
                    "description": "We use neither before a singular noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I could not choose between them - I liked them ...........................",
                    "description": "Both means one and the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................. Mark nor Samuel passed the test.",
                    "description": "We neither before nor.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Both",
                        "Either",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ................................ liked the movie.",
                    "description": "Both means one and the other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ................................... sings and dances.",
                    "description": "We use both before and.",
                    "answers": [
                        "both",
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ..................................... sings nor dances.",
                    "description": "We use neither before nor.",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "neither",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}